

Objective

I have the good knowledge from university and self-teach, it helps me the stable foundation, problem solving mindset. So with my experience, i can work with teachers, guide students in studying effectively, quickly as teaching assistant, contribute to the company all my best.

Education

Ton Duc Thang University [Sep 2018 - 2022]

Major: Computer Science

GPA: 7.46/10

Work experience

University [2018 - 2021]

Big exercise, final project in subject.

- I have the experience in some programing languages, such as: python, java, c, html, css.
- Develop project using framework to build api, ui website. And some concept ideal in machine learning.

Activities

University [2018 - 2019]

Young Men's Health

- I take part in the activity 2 years, 2018 and 2019.

University [2018 - 2020]

ICON club

- I join the ICON club for IT major, where such activities in, program competitions, make new friends, make team up, join discord to chat....

Contact information

Oct 27, 2000 0393258535 tienle676@gmail.com Ba Ria Vung Tau, Vietnam

Certifications

TOEIC Certificate with score 645 [2019]

Python (Basic) Certificate in HackerRank [2020]

Problem solving (Intermediate)
Certificate in HackerRank [2020]

Honors & Awards

2nd rank in RECURSION competitionorganized by ICON club in Ton DucThang University [2021]

Skills

Python
Office
Logical thinking and creative
Research reading
Public Speaking

Interests

Music Reading
Badminton